<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<class name="AutoworkLogger" inherits="RefCounted" experimental="Some methods may not be implemented and may be changed in future versions." xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../doc/class.xsd">
	<brief_description>
		Handles logging and reporting of test results.
	</brief_description>
	<description>
		The AutoworkLogger is responsible for collecting, formatting, and exporting test results produced by the Autowork framework.

		It records passes, failures, and warnings during test execution and keeps track of statistics such as total tests and orphaned objects.
		The logger can output results to the console as well as export them to structured formats like JSON and JUnit XML for integration with external tools and CI pipelines.
	</description>
	<tutorials>
	</tutorials>
	<methods>
		<method name="add_fail">
			<return type="void" />
			<param index="0" name="message" type="String" />
			<description>
				Records a failed assertion or test.

				The provided [param message] typically describes the reason for the failure and is stored for reporting and output.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="add_pass">
			<return type="void" />
			<param index="0" name="message" type="String" />
			<description>
				Records a successful assertion or test.

				The provided [param message] may contain additional context or confirmation of the passing condition.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="add_warning">
			<return type="void" />
			<param index="0" name="message" type="String" />
			<description>
				Records a warning generated during test execution.

				Warnings do not cause a test to fail but indicate potential issues or unexpected conditions.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="export_json">
			<return type="bool" />
			<param index="0" name="file_path" type="String" />
			<description>
				Exports the collected test results to a JSON file.

				The file at [param file_path] will contain a structured representation of all logged results and statistics.
				Returns [code]true[/code] if the export succeeds, otherwise [code]false[/code].
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="export_xml">
			<return type="bool" />
			<param index="0" name="file_path" type="String" />
			<description>
				Exports the collected test results in JUnit XML format.

				The generated file can be used by continuous integration systems and reporting tools.
				Returns [code]true[/code] if the export succeeds, otherwise [code]false[/code].
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="inc_orphans">
			<return type="void" />
			<param index="0" name="count" type="int" />
			<description>
				Increments the number of orphaned objects detected during testing.

				Orphans typically refer to objects that were not properly freed or cleaned up, which may indicate memory management issues.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="inc_test_count">
			<return type="void" />
			<description>
				Increments the total number of executed tests.

				This is usually called internally as each test case begins or completes.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="print_summary">
			<return type="void" />
			<description>
				Prints a summary of the test results.

				The summary typically includes counts of passed, failed, and pending tests, along with warnings and other relevant statistics.
			</description>
		</method>
	</methods>
</class>
