<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<class name="AutoworkStubParams" inherits="RefCounted" experimental="Some methods may not be implemented and may be changed in future versions." xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../doc/class.xsd">
	<brief_description>
		Fluent configuration object for defining stub behavior.
	</brief_description>
	<description>
		The AutoworkStubParams class provides a fluent API for defining conditional stub behavior in tests.

		It is used by [AutoworkStubber] to describe how a method should behave when called, including return values, argument matching, or whether the original method should be executed.
	</description>
	<tutorials>
	</tutorials>
	<methods>
		<method name="to_call_super">
			<return type="AutoworkStubParams" />
			<description>
				Configures the stub to call the original method implementation.

				When applied, the stub will allow execution of the original method instead of fully replacing it.
				This is useful for partial overrides or behavior extension.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="to_do_nothing">
			<return type="AutoworkStubParams" />
			<description>
				Configures the stub to do nothing when the method is called.

				The method call is intercepted and suppressed, and no return value or original implementation is executed.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="to_return">
			<return type="AutoworkStubParams" />
			<param index="0" name="value" type="Variant" />
			<description>
				Configures the stub to return a specific value.

				When the method is called, the provided [param value] is returned instead of executing the original implementation.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="when_passed">
			<return type="AutoworkStubParams" />
			<param index="0" name="args" type="Variant" />
			<description>
				Restricts the stub to only apply when specific arguments are passed.

				The stub will only be triggered if the method call matches the provided [param args].
				This allows fine-grained control over conditional behavior.
			</description>
		</method>
	</methods>
</class>
