<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<class name="AutoworkSignalWatcher" inherits="RefCounted" experimental="Some methods may not be implemented and may be changed in future versions." xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../doc/class.xsd">
	<brief_description>
		Tracks and records signal emissions during tests.
	</brief_description>
	<description>
		The AutoworkSignalWatcher is used to observe signals emitted by objects during test execution.

		It allows registering specific signals (or all signals from an object) and keeps a record of their emissions, including how many times they were triggered and with what arguments.
		This makes it possible to assert that signals were emitted as expected.
	</description>
	<tutorials>
	</tutorials>
	<methods>
		<method name="clear">
			<return type="void" />
			<description>
				Clears all recorded signal emissions and watched signals.

				After calling this method, the watcher returns to an empty state.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="did_emit">
			<return type="bool" />
			<param index="0" name="object" type="Object" />
			<param index="1" name="signal" type="StringName" />
			<description>
				Returns [code]true[/code] if the specified [param signal] was emitted by [param object].

				This checks whether at least one emission has been recorded since the last [method clear] call.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="get_emissions">
			<return type="Array" />
			<param index="0" name="object" type="Object" />
			<param index="1" name="signal" type="StringName" />
			<description>
				Returns an [Array] of recorded emissions for the given [param object] and [param signal].

				Each entry typically contains the arguments passed when the signal was emitted.
				The exact structure may depend on the implementation.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="watch_signal">
			<return type="void" />
			<param index="0" name="object" type="Object" />
			<param index="1" name="signal" type="StringName" />
			<description>
				Starts watching a specific signal on the given [param object].

				All future emissions of the specified signal will be recorded until [method clear] is called or the watcher is reset.
			</description>
		</method>
		<method name="watch_signals">
			<return type="void" />
			<param index="0" name="object" type="Object" />
			<description>
				Starts watching all signals emitted by the given [param object].

				This is useful when the exact signal names are not known in advance or when multiple signals need to be tracked simultaneously.
			</description>
		</method>
	</methods>
</class>
