<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<class name="SixWayLightingMaterial" inherits="Material" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../doc/class.xsd">
	<brief_description>
		A [b]Volumetric Lighting Shader[/b] using a Six-Directional Lighting Model (SDLM).
	</brief_description>
	<description>
		A [b]Volumetric Lighting Shader[/b] using a Six-Directional Lighting Model (SDLM) designed to simulate realistic light interaction within semi-transparent volumes like cloud, smoke, fog and fire.
		[b]Parameters :[/b]
		[color=#03c2fc][b]Six Way Map RTB[/b][/color] (Type: Texture2D): Right-Top-Back lighting texture (RGB channels contain lighting data for positive X, Y, and negative Z directions).
		[color=#03c2fc][b]Six Way Map LBF[/b][/color] (Type: Texture2D): Left-Bottom-Front lighting texture (RGB channels contain lighting data for negative X, negative Y, and positive Z directions).
		[color=#03c2fc][b]Six Way Map TEA[/b][/color] (Type: Texture2D): Transparency-Emission-AO texture (R channel for Alpha, G for Emission, B for Ambient Occlusion).
		[color=#03c2fc][b]Normal Map[/b][/color] (Type: Texture2D): Normal map for simulating surface details.
		[color=#03c2fc][b]Emission Ramp[/b][/color] (Type: Texture2D): Color ramp texture for emission effects. Blackbody can be used as well.
		[color=#fcba03][b]Absorption[/b][/color] (Type: Color): Light absorption color, Defines how much light is absorbed by the volume.
		[color=#fcba03][b]Thickness[/b][/color] (Type: float): Volume thickness multiplier (Affects light absorption).
		[color=#fcba03][b]Density[/b][/color] (Type: float): Density of the volume (Affects overall opacity).
		[color=#fcba03][b]Scattering[/b][/color] (Type: float): Light scattering amount, Defines how much light diffuses through the volume.
		[color=#fcba03][b]Normal Power[/b][/color] (Type: float): Strength of normal mapping effect.
		[color=#fcba03][b]Normal Blend[/b][/color] (Type: float): Blend factor between directional lighting and normal-mapped lighting.
		[color=#fcba03][b]AO Power[/b][/color] (Type: float): Ambient occlusion strength from the TEA texture's B channel.
		[color=#fcba03][b]emission_power[/b][/color] (Type: float): Emission strength multiplier.
		[color=#fcba03][b]Billboard Mode[/b][/color] (Type: bool): Enables billboarding (face towards camera).
		[color=#fcba03][b]Billboard y-Axis Only[/b][/color] (Type: bool): Billboard only around Y-axis (for trees/vertical objects).
		[color=#fcba03][b]billboard Keep Scale[/b][/color] (Type: bool): Maintain object scale when billboarding.
		[color=#fcba03][b]Animate[/b][/color] (Type: bool): Enables flipbook animation.
		[color=#fcba03][b]Animate Speed[/b][/color] (Type: float): Flipbook animation speed in frames per second.
		[color=#fcba03][b]Animate Offset[/b][/color] (Type: float): Time offset for animation start.
		[color=#fcba03][b]Flipbook Dimensions[/b][/color] (Type: Vector2): Grid dimensions for flipbook animation (columns, rows).
		[color=#03fc84][b]Developed By Hamid.Memar[/b][/color]
	</description>
	<tutorials>
	</tutorials>
</class>
